### Contact

Dublin, Ireland +353833090006 (Mobile) val.paz@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/valeriapaz-40304b45 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/valeriapaz (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

3D Studio Max

**VRay** 

Marvelous Designer

### Languages

Portuguese

**English** 

#### Certifications

**Autodesk Certification** 

# Valeria Paz

Computer Science Student

Ireland

### Summary

With my background in Mathematics I found myself drawn to 3D visualization in 2008. Marrying my artistic and technical skills has been successful for me when working on projects from architecture, to retail spaces, and expositions.

I'm excited to continue to grow professionally while adding value to the Dublin market in the city I now call home.

Passionated about games, design and programming.

## Experience

OCS, One Complete Solution Security Guard September 2020 - Present (8 months)

Self employed Freelance 3D Artist September 2017 - Present (3 years 8 months) County Dublin, Ireland

Starbucks
Supervisor
July 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 3 months)
County Dublin, Ireland

SRCOM Ilustradora 3D August 2016 - February 2017 (7 months) São Paulo e Região, Brasil

Caseludico
Ilustradora 3D
October 2008 - December 2015 (7 years 3 months)

Sao Paulo, Brazil

Criacitta Marketing Cenografico Ilustradora 3D June 2008 - October 2008 (5 months)

## Education

Dorset College Dublin

Bachelor of Science in Computing, Computer Science · (2019 - 2022)

Universidade Guarulhos

Bacharel em Matemática, Mathematics · (2003 - 2005)

Cadritech, Melies